{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453186387","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453186386"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" cc72e008-8897-4f29-bf34-ac193f4b9701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453191200","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453191200"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" cc72e008-8897-4f29-bf34-ac193f4b9701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453195346","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453195346"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" cc72e008-8897-4f29-bf34-ac193f4b9701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453199183","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453199183"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" cc72e008-8897-4f29-bf34-ac193f4b9701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453202936","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453202936"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" cc72e008-8897-4f29-bf34-ac193f4b9701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453211106","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453211106"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" cc72e008-8897-4f29-bf34-ac193f4b9701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453218858","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453218858"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" cc72e008-8897-4f29-bf34-ac193f4b9701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453239726","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453239726"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" cc72e008-8897-4f29-bf34-ac193f4b9701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453262644","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453262644"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" cc72e008-8897-4f29-bf34-ac193f4b9701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453266313","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453266312"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" cc72e008-8897-4f29-bf34-ac193f4b9701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453270532","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453270532"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" cc72e008-8897-4f29-bf34-ac193f4b9701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453274576","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453274576"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" cc72e008-8897-4f29-bf34-ac193f4b9701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_B-R-K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453278090","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453278090"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" cc72e008-8897-4f29-bf34-ac193f4b9701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453281887","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453281887"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" cc72e008-8897-4f29-bf34-ac193f4b9701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-W-N"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453286549","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453286549"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" cc72e008-8897-4f29-bf34-ac193f4b9701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453298584","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453298584"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" cc72e008-8897-4f29-bf34-ac193f4b9701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453310490","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453310490"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" cc72e008-8897-4f29-bf34-ac193f4b9701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-D-R"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453317777","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453317777"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" cc72e008-8897-4f29-bf34-ac193f4b9701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-P-B"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453332157","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453332157"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" cc72e008-8897-4f29-bf34-ac193f4b9701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_e-S-n"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453339944","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453339944"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" cc72e008-8897-4f29-bf34-ac193f4b9701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-J-F"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453355321","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453355321"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" cc72e008-8897-4f29-bf34-ac193f4b9701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453360974","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453360973"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" cc72e008-8897-4f29-bf34-ac193f4b9701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-U-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453365836","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453365836"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" cc72e008-8897-4f29-bf34-ac193f4b9701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453376189","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453376189"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" cc72e008-8897-4f29-bf34-ac193f4b9701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453383508","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453383507"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" cc72e008-8897-4f29-bf34-ac193f4b9701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453389338","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453389338"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" cc72e008-8897-4f29-bf34-ac193f4b9701"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.rand","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453408588","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453408588"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" be5ab850-2597-44e0-9794-76f2d44c5bf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.rand"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_2_0_5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.rand","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453415248","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453415248"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" be5ab850-2597-44e0-9794-76f2d44c5bf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.rand"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_9_2_7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.rand","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453421937","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453421937"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" be5ab850-2597-44e0-9794-76f2d44c5bf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.rand"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_10_7_1"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.rand","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453428666","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453428666"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" be5ab850-2597-44e0-9794-76f2d44c5bf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.rand"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_3_5_0"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.rand","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453435329","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453435329"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" be5ab850-2597-44e0-9794-76f2d44c5bf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.rand"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_3_0_10"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.rand","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453441997","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453441996"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" be5ab850-2597-44e0-9794-76f2d44c5bf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.rand"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_1_9_0"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.rand","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453448712","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453448711"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" be5ab850-2597-44e0-9794-76f2d44c5bf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.rand"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_8_6_9"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.rand","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453455369","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453455369"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" be5ab850-2597-44e0-9794-76f2d44c5bf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.rand"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_2_0_3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.rand","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453462891","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453462891"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" be5ab850-2597-44e0-9794-76f2d44c5bf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.rand"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_2_0_3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.rand","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453469592","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453469591"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" be5ab850-2597-44e0-9794-76f2d44c5bf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.rand"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_9_4_2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.rand","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453477095","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453477095"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" be5ab850-2597-44e0-9794-76f2d44c5bf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.rand"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_9_4_2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.rand","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453486205","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453486205"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" be5ab850-2597-44e0-9794-76f2d44c5bf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.rand"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_9_4_2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.rand","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453495140","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453495140"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" be5ab850-2597-44e0-9794-76f2d44c5bf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.rand"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_9_4_2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453519229","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453519229"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NDEVU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEVU"," userResponse":" NDEVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453524470","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453524469"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NDEVU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEVU"," userResponse":" NDEVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453526108","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453526108"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NJIWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIWA"," userResponse":" NJIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453530239","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453530238"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NJIWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIWA"," userResponse":" NJIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453531832","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453531832"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NGUMI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUMI"," userResponse":" NGUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453539584","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453539584"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NGUMI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453541174","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453541174"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NGURUWE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGURUWE"," userResponse":" NGURUWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453546342","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453546341"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NGURUWE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGURUWE"," userResponse":" NGURUWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453547897","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453547897"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453550267","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453550267"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453551825","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453551825"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZI"," userResponse":" NAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453560202","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453560202"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZI"," userResponse":" NAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453561850","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453561850"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYWELE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453567761","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453567761"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYWELE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453569387","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453569387"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYATI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYATI"," userResponse":" NYATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453576660","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453576659"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYATI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYATI"," userResponse":" NYATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453578354","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453578354"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" NYANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453583353","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453583352"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" NYANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453584901","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453584901"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NGOMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOMA"," userResponse":" NGOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453589367","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453589367"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NGOMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOMA"," userResponse":" NGOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453590936","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453590935"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NDIZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453595823","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453595821"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NDIZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453597431","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453597430"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYANYA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453599939","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453599939"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYANYA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453601560","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453601560"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYAYO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAYO"," userResponse":" NYAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453604477","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453604477"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYAYO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAYO"," userResponse":" NYAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453606085","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453606085"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NGUO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUO"," userResponse":" NGUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453611187","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453611187"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NGUO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUO"," userResponse":" NGUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453612785","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453612785"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NG'OMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453612795","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453612794"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NG'OMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453615456","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453615456"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NG'OMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453616234","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453616234"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NG'OMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453617996","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453617996"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NG'OMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453619565","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453619564"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYAMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453622564","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453622564"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYAMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453624133","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453624133"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NDEGE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453632620","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453632619"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NDEGE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453634203","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453634203"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYUMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453682473","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453682471"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" NYUMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453682626","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453682626"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYUMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453828036","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453828034"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" 65f60022-3214-400d-abe8-c4d226449834"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" NYUMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453828161","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453828161"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" a3ea36e4-2e93-444c-9e55-88efab8bb71a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOTOKEA"," userResponse":" KILICHOTOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453994124","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453994124"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" a3ea36e4-2e93-444c-9e55-88efab8bb71a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453994225","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453994225"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_143918"," gameId":" ef9ca4de-65cf-4ce4-8ea4-41fcd52bd1b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOTOKEA"," userResponse":" KILICHOTOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}